God, you're beautiful.
Why are we fighting this?
You know you want it
to happen as much as I do.
I want you.
I need you.
Let me make love to you.
Now, I don't want
to stand in the way
of true love or anything,
but I think a cantaloupe
might hurt less.
No, I'm, uh...
I'm rehearsing my lines.
They're giving me a big romantic
story on Days of Our Lives.
It's the first time
my character's gotten one.
I'm so nervous, you know?
I really want it to be good.
Wow.
I haven't seen you
this worked up
since you did
that dog food commercial
and you thought you were going
to be with a real talking dog.
Yeah, that was a disappointment.
Ooh, hey.
You want to come down to the set
and tell me if I'm
doing okay?
Are you serious?
Yeah, yeah.
You just have to promise
not to get yourself
thrown out again.
That was an honest mistake.
Right.
"Oh, my God.
Is this the men's room?
"I feel so foolish.
Have you always known
you wanted to be an actor?"
Yeah, that was an awesome day.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
Hi.
So, do you guys want
to come and eat dinner
at the restaurant sometime
in the next few weeks?
Sure, yeah.
Oh, we'd love to.
Well, you can't.
We're booked solid
for the next month.
Well, I can't
give you a massage
because my license
has been revoked again.
Phoebe, what happened?
Well, it was an accident.
You know, it's a lot of oil
and sometimes
the hand just slips.
Have I got a surprise for you.
Pack your bags.
Oh, no.
You guys aren't supposed
to get divorced for seven years.
What? No.
I'm taking Monica
to a romantic inn in Vermont.
Oh, good.
Okay.
Good for you.
Trying to recapture the magic.
Good.
So, what
do you say?
Can you get
out of work?
Oh, honey, I can't.
I was just telling these guys
that things are crazy
at the restaurant.
You're really that busy?
Yeah. I'm sorry, I really am.
Well,
that's okay.
I'll just, uh,
try and reschedule.
Hi, this is Chandler Bing.
I made a reservation there
and I need to change it.
Well, what do you mean
it's nonrefundable?
Well, can I just come
some other time?
Well, can't you
make an exception?
Tell them I'm a chef
at a big New York restaurant.
And tell them that in two weeks,
I will once again
be a masseuse in good standing.
Look, this is ridiculous.
I'm not paying
for that room, okay?
Well thank you very much.
Yeah, I'm going to Vermont.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Just use your
travel insurance.
I don't have travel insurance.
Well, this
is what happens
when people
live on the edge.
Why don't you take Ross?
Don't you think that'll
be a little weird?
I mean, two guys
in a romantic inn?
No, not if the room
has two beds.
I guess.
Still seems a little...
Moonlight boat ride!
Hey, Joey, is this the bed
where Olivia
lost her virginity?
I don't know, but one
of the extras sure did.
Hey, listen, Rach.
Thanks again for coming
down to watch my scenes.
Oh, please, honey.
Just the fact that you
want me here to support you...
Oh, my God.
Is that Christian Saunders?
He is so gorgeous.
Also, so gay.
Well...
in my head, he's done some
pretty not-gay stuff.
Well, at the Christmas party,
him and Santa did some
definitely-gay stuff.
MAN:
Joey.
Joey, we're ready for you.
Okay.
All right,
wish me luck.
Okay.
Well, not that you
need it, but good...
God! Is that
Chase Lassiter?
Oh, now he's straight,
right?
Rach, I got to say,
if you weren't here wondering
if these guys were gay,
I don't know if I could do this.
I'm sorry, you're right.
I'm sorry. Good luck.
Thanks.
And... action!
Drake, what are
you doing here?
Stopping you
from marrying the wrong man
and making the biggest
mistake of your life.
Get out.
You don't love him.
What do you know about love?
I know what I felt that night
when we kissed under the bridge.
That kiss
never happened.
Well what about
this one?
( gasps )
Now I told you
to get out.
Fine,
I'll go.
But let me ask you
one question.
You look real familiar.
Have we...
Shh!
He's asking her a question.
Can you really live
the rest of your life
never knowing what
we could have been?
I don't have a choice.
Yes, you do.
I'm the one who doesn't
have a choice because I...
because I can't
stop loving you.
Don't say that.
Tell me to stop.
Just... tell me to stop.
Cut!
No!
Or cut, you know,
that's your call.
Everything was delicious.
Thank you.
It was.
The duck in particular
was superb.
Thank you.
You haven't said anything.
Actually, I do have
one small complaint.
Oh. Well, please, I...
I welcome criticism.
Your musician--
right outside the restaurant--
is kind of a mood-killer.
What musician?
♪ And there's a country
called Argentina ♪
♪ It's a place I've never seen ♪
♪ But I'm told for 50 pesos ♪
♪ You can buy a human spleen ♪
♪ Human spleen... ♪
♪ Olé! ♪
What are you doing here?
Well, you said you had customers
lined up in the streets,
so I'm here to entertain.
Oh, great.
Yeah!
It really has
been great, too.
You know, some of these people
must have seen me play before,
because they were requesting
a bunch of my songs.
Yeah, "You Suck" and, um...
"Shut Up and Go Home."
Um, listen, Phoebe...
Yeah?
You know how much I love
listening to your music.
You know, but...
But what?
Um, well, this is kind
of a classy place.
Okay, say no more.
♪ It wasn't just
that she was fat ♪
♪ The woman smelled
like garbage ♪
Everyone!
♪ It wasn't just
that she was fat ♪
♪ The woman smelled
like garbage. ♪
Classy, huh?
Hi. Chandler Bing.
I have a reservation.
Welcome to
the Chestnut Inn, Mr. Bing.
So where are you
joining us from?
New York.
The Big Apple!
I'm sorry.
He's a little bit wound up.
We had to stop at every maple
candy stand on the way here.
I ate all my gifts
for everybody!
I'm sorry, Mr. Bing,
there's no record
of your reservation
in the computer.
Well, that's impossible.
Can you check again,
please?
( falsetto ):
Can you check
again, please?
I'm sorry. It's not here.
It's not there.
Let me get this straight.
I called yesterday
to try to cancel
my reservation
and was told
it's not refundable.
Then we drove six hours
all the way up here,
and now you're telling me that
we don't have a reservation?
I don't know what to say.
She doesn't know
what to say.
Just give us
the cheapest room you have.
Well, unfortunately,
the only thing
we have available
is our deluxe suite.
The rate is $600.
That's insane!
That is totally insane.
Dude, let's drive home.
We'll hit all the
maple candy stores
on the way back,
and if they're closed,
maybe we'll tap a tree
and make some ourselves.
Does that room have a closet
I can lock him in?
We'll take it.
Great.
They are totally
ripping us off!
Dude, don't worry about it.
I know how we can make
your money back.
This is a nice hotel, you know.
Plenty of amenities.
We just load up on those.
Like those apples.
Instead of taking one,
um... I take six.
Great. At $100 an apple,
we're there.
Come on, you get the idea.
You know, we'll make our
money back in no time.
Dude, you're shaking.
I think it's the sugar.
Can you hold the apple?
Hi.
Hey.
Joey, I got to tell you:
I have been thinking all day
about that scene you did.
I mean, you
were amazing.
Oh, you know,
the writing was good,
you know,
and the director's good,
and-and my co-star's good,
but they're not as good as me!
Come on, you have to tell me
what happens tomorrow.
Oh, just going over
the script now.
Do you want to read lines
with me?
Me? Oh, I... I'm not an actress.
Oh, well, I can ask Monica.
Screw her! That part is mine.
Right.
Okay, so, uh, so just from
the top of the page, right here.
Okay.
( inhales deeply )
"Hello, Drake.
I'm surprised
to see you here."
"I can't believe
you married him."
"Well, what choice
did I have?
He was keeping my
sister in a dungeon."
So what about us?
Everything we feel
for each other?"
"It's over.
You have to accept that."
"How can I?
"Knowing I'll never hold you
in my arms again?
"Or touch your skin
or feel your lips?
"Knowing I'll never
make love to you?
How can I accept that"
"I can never kiss you again
when it's all I can do
not to kiss you right now?"
Kiss me.
What?
Uh, Rach, it doesn't say that.
No, I'm saying it.
But... but...
Just... don't talk.
( gasping ):
Oh!
Well, that's new.
Hi.
This is Ross Geller
in suite 206.
Um, I seem to have forgotten
a couple of things.
Could-could you have some
complimentary toiletries
sent up to my room?
Thank you.
Okay, um, toothbrush,
toothpaste,
razor, mouthwash, deodorant,
dental floss, Band-Aids,
shaving cream, aftershave...
and I feel
like I'm forgetting something.
Um, is there anything else
you have
that I haven't asked for
already?
Yeah. Go ahead.
Send up some tampons.
Thank you.
( catching his breath )
What did you get?
USA Today.
Nice. Put it
with the others.
And I also got...
two more apples.
We're four short of a bushel.
God, I feel so alive!
I love being
in the country.
I also got
these great
salt and pepper shakers
from the restaurant.
Ooh, that's not cool.
Dude, none of this is cool.
Look, Chandler,
you have to find the line
between stealing and-and taking
what the hotel owes you.
Um, for example,
a hair dryer-- no, no, no.
But shampoos and
conditioners--
oh, yes, yes, yes.
Now, the-the
salt shaker
is off-limits. Uh!
But the salt...
I wish I'd thought this through.
I think I get
what you mean, though.
Like, the lamp is, uh,
is the hotel's,
but the bulbs...
Oh, you already got that?
Not my first time
in a hotel, my friend.
Okay, uh,
how about this?
No, no, no.
You can't
take the remote control.
Yes, but the batteries.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Ooh, ooh. Let's-let's celebrate
with some maple candy.
No!
At least tell me
where you hid it.
Can I ask you a question?
Yeah.
Have you ever had any...
weird... romantic... dreams?
Hmm. Let me think.
Oh.
When I was younger,
I used to dream
that I got married
to Mayor McCheese.
And-and on our wedding
night, I ate his head.
Okay.
Well, this is like that...
in no way.
I had a...
I had a dream last night
that I wanted to kiss Joey.
Wow.
You mean, like, like,
"kiss him" kiss him?
Oh, yeah.
I mean,
it was pretty intense.
Wow.
What do you think
brought that on?
I don't know.
Maybe it has something
to do with the fact
that I saw him
do a love scene yesterday.
A love scene?
With-with who?
Olivia.
Olivia?!
I thought she was
marrying Connor?
Oh.
Oh, right.
Real life more important.
So, do you think
that my dream means anything?
I don't know.
I mean, you saw him
do a love scene.
So, maybe you don't
have a thing for Joey.
Maybe you have
a thing for Drake.
Huh.
Well, it was Joey
reading Drake's lines
in the dream.
Of course it was.
Trust me.
When it comes
to psychology,
I know what I'm
talking about.
I took two psych
classes in college.
Oh.
You took the same class twice.
It was hard.
I...
Hey.
Hi.
Here, Monica.
Look what I
got to wear
when I play at
your restaurant.
Ha!
Uh, uh.
Wait.
Right?
I think this might even class up
"The Ballad
of the Uncircumcised Man."
Um... Phoebe?
Hmm?
Maybe I wasn't clear before.
But I really love
listening to your music here,
but my restaurant--
it's sort of an upscale place.
Right, yeah, okay.
I'll ask the butler to fetch
my diamonds out of the vault.
Phoebe, it's not
what you wear...
it's sort of your songs.
I just don't think you should
play at the restaurant anymore.
Oh.
Okay.
Fine, I'll just... I'll...
I'll take the hat back.
There.
Hey.
So, you guys, the funniest thing
happened at work...
What, my songs aren't good
enough for your restaurant?
Okay, we're still on that.
I didn't say your songs
weren't good enough.
Well, then what's wrong
with them?
What, they don't go with
your tiny portions
of pretentious food?
Tiny portions?
Yeah, well, um, "Excuse me,
"I ordered the smoked
salmon appetizer.
But I can't see it.
I can't see it."
Phoebe, it's not about quantity.
Well, it's not about quality.
Oh... oh, really?
You want to talk
about quality?
Have you ever heard of "a key"?
It's what some people sing in.
Well, at least all my songs
don't taste like garlic.
Yeah, there are
other ingredients, Monica.
Oh, okay, so that's
what we're doing.
Well, you know what,
when I'm in the coffeehouse
bopping along
to one of your songs,
I'm wearing ear plugs.
Ear plugs? Or cloves of garlic?
You know what?
I take back
what I said before.
You keep playing
at the restaurant.
Because with your music
driving people inside,
my bar sales
have gone up like crazy.
What are people having,
the garlic martini?!
Here's your copy
of the bill.
We hope you
enjoyed your stay.
Oh, we did.
And you still have
all your lamps.
Well, I didn't
factor in the room tax.
Oh, dude, don't
worry about it.
I found an unattended
maid's cart.
We're way ahead
of the game.
Oh, my God.
What?
There's something new
in the bowl.
Look, we have enough.
Just walk away.
But I-I want...
I want the pine cones.
There's a forest
right outside.
It's not the same.
Okay, go quick.
( caws )
Thank you for
a delightful stay.
Oh, my maple candy!
♪ The food here at Javu ♪
♪ Will kill you ♪
Oh, thank God
it's just you.
I thought someone
was swinging a bag of cats
against the wall.
You better get back
in that kitchen, Monica.
The garlic's not going
to overuse itself.
Okay, you have
to stop playing now.
Why? The only person my playing
is bothering is you.
Oh, yeah?
Okay, let's settle this.
Come on.
Get your garlic peelers off me.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hi, I'm Monica Gellar.
I'm the head chef here.
Okay, I was actually
expecting a little
applause there,
but whatever. Okay.
Okay, quick question:
By a show of hands,
how many of you were bothered
by this woman's singing outside?
Okay, okay.
How many of you enjoyed
the music outside?
Ha.
All right.
Let me ask you
this question.
How many of you thought
the music was fine
but not in keeping with
the tone of the restaurant?
Okay, well...
who identified the tone
of this restaurant
as pretentious comma garlicky?
Okay. Who thinks
the food is delicious
and a little pretension
never hurt anyone?
Okay, well, all right.
Who thinks the food is fine,
the music was fine,
but your evening was ruined
by this incessant poll taking?
Excuse us.
All right,
here's a question.
Who was so worried about
her restaurant being fancy
that she made a big deal about
her friend playing her music
and feels really bad
about it now?
Oh.
Well, who was so stupid
and stubborn
that she lashed out
against her friend's cooking
which she actually thinks
is pretty great?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Hey, you want
to stick around
and I'll whip you up
some dinner?
Yeah, as long as it's free.
Food here is
ridiculously overpr...
Who's hoping the hand-raising
thing is still cute enough
that you won't hate me?
Hey.
Joey...
do you have peanut butter
on the back of your head?
Oh, man, I thought
I got it all.
How...?
How?
Well, I was making
a peanut butter smoothie, right.
And I couldn't find the...
this little plastic
thingy that goes in
the top of the blender.
And I thought, well, you know,
"How important can be, right?"
It turns out, very.
Wow.
Definitely just Drake.
What?
How's it going with Drake?
Oh.
I don't think
it's going very well.
What?
That scene I saw was so good.
Well, I'm feeling really
insecure about the one
we're shooting tomorrow.
Joey, is this that thing that
you do when you say you're bad,
so I'll give you a compliment?
A little.
No, but I really
am worried.
I mean, I have
to make it convincing that...
that I'm in love with Olivia.
So?
So, I've never played that.
Oh, honey,
it can't be that hard.
I mean, you've been
in love before.
Uh, well... just once.
With you.
Okay.
This could be a little awkward.
I'm just going to blow past it.
Well, can't you just use
that method, that actor thing
where you use
your real-life memories
to help you in your performance?
What the hell are you
talking about?
All right.
All right, look, just, um...
just try to remember how
you felt when you were in love
and think about that
when you're playing the scene.
Oh.
Okay.
Yeah.
I think I can do that.
Yeah, okay.
There's this party scene
coming up
and Olivia and
her husband are there
and all Drake wants to do
is grab her and kiss her,
but he can't.
And that makes me think about
all those times
I wanted to grab you and
kiss you, but you didn't know,
so I would just pretend
everything was cool,
but really it was killing me.
Joey, you never...
you never talked about
that before.
Hey, you know what else
I could use?
There's this scene where Drake
sneaks into Olivia's bedroom
and she doesn't know
he's there--
which never happened with us.
He knows he shouldn't
be there,
but he just wants
to look at her, you know.
And I remember
all those mornings
before you even
put on your makeup
when I would think to myself,
"My God, she is beautiful."
And it hurt so much
because I knew
I could never tell you.
But it was worth it just
to be there looking at you.
Thanks, dude.
This is great!
( door closes )
Besides tampons and salt?
Oh. Oh, my God.
Maple candy.
That's so sweet of you.
Mmm...
That's weird; it's empty.
Hi, you guys.
What's going on?
You-you guys want
to hang out or...?
Do you, do you guys
hear a buzzing?
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org